

Amaury Grotard

Bachelor Student

CONTACT

- +32 497 77 84 87
- 😭 contact@amaury.xyz
- 1380 LASNE

EDUCATION

Bachelor in I.T

EPHEC | Louvain-la-Neuve

Sept. 2021 - Present

C.E.S.S in Social Sciences

ARRIX | Rixensart

Sept. 2014 - June 2021

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Communication
- Flexibility
- Attention to Detail

LANGUAGES

- French C2
- English C1
- Dutch A1

HOBBIES

- Video Games
- Programming
- Travelling

PROFILE SUMMARY

I'm a 21 years old bachelor student with a passion for computers. My ambition is to make it my vocation and deepen my knowledge in this fascinating field. I'm very comfortable with development, whether in Python or JavaScript in particular. I also have advanced knowledge of HTML, CSS and SQL. Aside from my studies, I'm an avid gamer and cybersecurity enthusiast. My aim is to continue to learn and grow in these fields, and perhaps one day make a significant contribution to the advancement of technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

System & Network Administration Intern

Feb. 2024 - May 2024

EPHEC | Louvain-la-Neuve

I've joined my school's IT department for 3 months to discover the work of a system administrator. I've been given the opportunity to work with Shibboleth to build an identity provider integrated with eduGAIN. I've also worked with virtual machines using VMWare's suite. The internship was very promising and I've learnt a lot of knowledge in virtualization and single sign-on.

Administrator & Secretary

Sept. 2023 - July 2024

EPHEC Student Council | Louvain-la-Neuve

I am an elected student of the EPHEC Student Council, called "CHE2". I act as administrator and secretary. The members of the EPHEC Student Council are elected annually by their peers, and represent all students at EPHEC in the various participatory bodies such as the Board of Management, the Pedagogical Council, the Category Council and the Social Council.

I.T Helpdesk Intern

Feb. 2021

MINAKEM | Mont-Saint-Guibert

I completed my sixth grade internship at a pharmaceutical company. It was an observation internship with an IT helpdesk technician. I learned a lot about how IT works in a company. This internship was very enriching and helped me confirm the path I wanted to follow.

EXTRACURRICULAR EXPERIENCE

CyberSecurity Challenge Belgium

Mar. 2023 & Mar. 2024

Online Qualifiers

I took part in the 2023 & 2024 editions of the CyberSecurity Challenge Belgium. We competed in a team of 4 against more than a thounsand of challengers. We finished in 59th place out of 289 teams. The second year, we finished in 60th position out of 290 teams. It wasn't enough to qualify, but I was very proud of where I was able to lead my team.